http://www.chreos.co.nz/index.php/privacy-policy

HomeAbout UsProductsChreosWebsitesPDAsPayfireOur CustomersServicesBlogContact Us
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We do not collect your information on this site.  We only know who you are if you send us an email via ‘Contact us’.
What do we use your information for?
Any information we collect from your use of the ‘Contact us’ page is used to facilitate communications between you and us.
This information will not be sold or passed on to other companies.
How do we protect your information?
Because the only information we collect is automatically sent as an email we provide no additional security around this data.  All emails and confidential information will be held securely by Wild Software Ltd.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 10 February 2014
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via the ‘Contact us’ page.
Chreos Business Solutions - Integrated for Growth (©) 2020 | Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions
Scroll to Top
